# Rafael Millan Rodriguez

rafmillan@ucdavis.edu | 805-660-2896 | rafmillan.github.io

Tairrillari@dcdavis.cdd | 005-000-2050 | Tairrilliari.giti1db.io

## **OBJECTIVE:**

Obtain an internship or research opportunity where I can utilize my computer science and engineering skills as well as my problem solving skills and attention to detail to further develop my abilities in the field of computer science.

## **EDUCATION:**

University of California: Davis 2018 - Present

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

Westlake High School 2015 - 2018

Thousand Oaks, CA. GPA: 4.3

# **COURSEWORK:**

Circuits I, II; Data Structures & Algorithms; Programming (Python); Object-Oriented Programing(C, C++); Intro to Engineering Design; Discrete Math for CS; Calculus.

#### PROJECTS:

Engineering Project: Environmental Monitoring System for UCD Greenhouse Fall 2018

 Designed and built a prototype for a monitoring system & display utilizing the Arduino & Raspberry Pi.

Github: github.com/rafmillan

# **EXPERIENCE:**

PAKMAIL, Davis CA 2019 - 2020

 Offering competitive shipping logistics for freight as well as personal shipping worldwide as well as managing customers' private mailboxes while providing excellent customer service.

Tillys, Sales Associate, Thousand Oaks, CA

2018 - 2019

- Provide excellent customer service assisting customers regarding merchandise selection; Promoting the *Tillys Rewards* loyalty program during customer interactions.

FBLA & Computer Science Club: Outreach Program Volunteer

2016 - 2018

- Taught basic computer programming concepts to elementary school kids in underprivileged areas using Scratch.

Math Tutor 2016 - 2019

- Math-related subjects, helping students improve their academic performance

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

Proficient in Python, Java, C, C++ & HTML; Experience with IOS Development using Swift; Strong object-oriented design skills, knowledge of data structures and algorithms;

# **ACTIVITIES & HONORS:**

UC Davis Computer Science Club

Westlake High School Swim Team, 2015- 2018 (Varsity 2017-2018)

- Marmonte League Championship 2015, 2016, 2017

Honor Roll Student award: 2015-2018

President's Education Awards Program: 2018